# **SANJU P S**

# **UI/UX DESIGNER & DEVELOPER**



**PORTFOLIO** 

## CONTACT

- 8714068917
- Perimbadari post, Mannarkkad,Palakkad

### **PROFILE SUMMARY**

I am a qualified and professional web developer with 1 years of experience in UI/UX Design & Development. Well-versed in technology and writing code to create systems that are reliable and user-friendly. Works well both as part of a team and independently

### EDUCATION

# 2019 - 2022 RABINDRANATH TAGORE UNIVERSITY

BCA
Bachelors in Computer Application

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **QINCORE LABS**

Junior Software Engineer

JUN 2023 - NOV 2023

DEC 2023 - JUN 2024

 Developing, testing, and maintaining software applications to meet client requirements. Collaborating with senior engineers and other team members to design and implement new features.

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe XD
- Figma (Software)
- HTML5
- Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)
- Bootstrap (Framework)
- JavaScript
- React.js
- Hooks
- Redux.js
- Git

# INTERNSHIP

#### **Futura Labs**

UI/UX Designer & Developer

- Website Designing
- Logo Designing
- HTML Conversion
- Single Page Application in React

### **Right Soft Options**

Python full stack Developer

- · Website Designing
- · Logo Designing
- HTML Conversion
- Single Page Application in React

# LANGUAGE

- English
- Malayalam
- Hindi

# PROFESSIONAL SKILL

- Web Designing
- Time Managment
- Problem-Solving
- Debugging
- Project Management Tools
- Strong Communication

2022